herschelsupply.com 2016-10-19

# Privacy Policy - Herschel Supply Co.

## Privacy Policy

##### Privacy Statement

This privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”) sets out the privacy policies and practices for Herschel Supply Co. and its subsidiaries and affiliates with respect to how Herschel Supply Co. collects personal information. It also describes how Herschel Supply Co. maintains, uses, and discloses personal information. This Privacy Policy applies to information collected from you by Herschel Supply Co. via this website and other websites operated or provided by Herschel Supply Co., and various subdomains (collectively, the “Sites”); and other places where or means by which we may collect personal information. This Privacy Policy also sets out how you can access certain information that Herschel Supply Co. may collect about you. In this Privacy Policy, “personal information” means information or opinion about an individual whose identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained from the information or opinion as further defined under applicable privacy laws, including, but not limited to, Your Contacts and other personal information collected through the Services.

Please note that the Sites may contain links to other third party websites that are not controlled or operated by Herschel Supply Co. This Privacy Policy does not apply to such third party websites, and Herschel Supply Co. is not responsible for the content of such third party websites or the privacy practices of such third parties. Therefore Herschel Supply Co. encourages you to request and review the privacy policies of any third parties before disclosing your personal information to such parties or when visiting such third party websites.

##### Consent

BY SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION TO HERSCHEL SUPPLY CO. OR ITS SERVICE PROVIDERS AND AGENTS, YOU AGREE THAT HERSCHEL SUPPLY CO. MAY COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND YOU CONSENT TO THE USE, DISCLOSURE AND TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND AS PERMITTED OR REQUIRED BY LAW. Subject to legal and contractual requirements, you may refuse or withdraw your consent to certain of the purposes identified herein at any time by contacting Herschel Supply Co. at the address provided below. If you refuse or withdraw your consent, you acknowledge that Herschel Supply Co. may not be able to provide you or continue to provide you with certain services or information which may be of value to you.

##### Revisions to This Privacy Policy

Herschel Supply Co. reserves the right, in Herschel Supply Co.’s discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time, without prior notice to you. However, Herschel Supply Co. will treat your continued use of the Sites and Services following such revision as your acceptance of the revised terms. All revisions will be posted to the Sites and will apply to any personal information collected on or after the date posted. Herschel Supply Co. will obtain the necessary consents required under applicable privacy laws if it seeks to collect, use or disclose your personal information for purposes other than those to which consent has been obtained unless otherwise required or permitted by law.

_This Privacy Policy was last updated July 9, 2013._

##### Collection of Your Information

Herschel Supply Co. may collect personal information in connection with your use or purchase of Herschel Supply Co.’s products and services, which may include information provided in connection with the following activities:

  * Registering or filling in forms on the Sites. This includes information you may provide when you request additional information about Herschel Supply Co.’s products and services or sign up to receive Herschel Supply Co.’s e-mail newsletters or coupons.
  * Purchasing any product or service from Herschel Supply Co.
  * Providing feedback or making other submissions to Herschel Supply Co.
  * Requesting information or assistance from Herschel Supply Co. Herschel Supply Co. may also keep a copy of any communications or correspondence you may send to it, including any e-mail communications.
  * Participating or responding to consumer survey or requests for consumer’s opinions, concerns, and preferences regarding Herschel Supply Co.’s products and services.
  * Participating in consumer contests, sweepstakes and other promotions.
  * Using other features of the Sites or Services that may be offered from time to time, and may require such information in order to utilize the feature (including but not limited to making a Submission as defined in the Terms of Use).

The personal information that Herschel Supply Co. may collect may include your name, username, password, email address, age, date of birth, gender, address, telephone number, credit card and debit card numbers (with expiration dates), personal preferences, and any other personal information that you choose to include in your profile, or in other communications to Herschel Supply Co. You represent and warrant that you have the right and authority or have obtained all necessary consents to provide any information, including any personal information of another individual, that is provided by you to Herschel Supply Co.

Herschel Supply Co. may also collect information that may not be personal information, which may include, but is not limited to, the frequency of user visits to the Sites and Services, the routes by which users access the Sites and Services and use of any hyperlinks available on the Sites and Services. Herschel Supply Co. or its service providers and agents may process and use this aggregate data for various purposes including, but not limited to, analysis of this data for trends and statistics, development of the Sites and Services and the Sites’ and Services’ features and offerings, assessing patterns of use, or planning and evaluating marketing initiatives. This information is gathered by certain tools and methods such as the collection of your IP address or the use of cookies and is maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form unless otherwise noted.

##### Cookies

Like many websites, Herschel Supply Co. utilizes “cookies” to maintain a record of your visit to the Sites and your use of the Services. A cookie is a small text file that is transferred by a web server and stored on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device. It can only be read by the server that sent it to you. This information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided Herschel Supply Co. with personal information.

Cookies help Herschel Supply Co. to improve the Sites and Services, and to deliver more personalized service by enabling Herschel Supply Co. to estimate audience size and usage patterns; to store information about your preferences; to speed up your searches and to recognize you when you return to the Sites or use the Services.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. If you would prefer to prevent your computer from accepting Herschel Supply Co.’s cookies, you may follow your Internet browser’s steps for doing so. Please note, however, that if you do disable cookies from your browser, you may not be able to access certain sections of the Sites or the Services.

##### IP Addresses

An IP address is a computer’s numeric address, by which it can be located within a network. Herschel Supply Co. may record your IP address when you visit or use services or features on the Sites. Herschel Supply Co. may use your IP address for the purposes noted above, and also to help diagnose problems with Herschel Supply Co.’s server, or to administer the Sites. Herschel Supply Co. may also use your IP address to identify you when Herschel Supply Co. feels it is necessary to enforce compliance with this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use, or to protect the Sites, Services, systems, information, employees, service providers, business partners, users, customers and others.

##### Protection of Your Information

To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy and facilitate the appropriate use of information, Herschel Supply Co. uses physical, technological and administrative procedures to protect the personal information that Herschel Supply Co. collects from loss, unauthorized access, modification, disclosure or other misuse.

Nevertheless, Internet or wireless transmissions are never completely private or secure. You understand that any messages or information you send to the Sites or through the Services may be read or intercepted by others. If you have any questions about the security of personal information collected by Herschel Supply Co., please contact: [privacyofficer@herschelsupply.com](mailto:privacyofficer@herschelsupply.com).

You should also be aware that certain aspects of the Sites and Services are not confidential and are available for public viewing. For example, any submissions that you may post to any publicly available blogs or other publicly available features of the Sites and Services are not confidential and may be viewed by other users of the Sites and Services. By making personal information publicly available where the Sites and Services allow you to do so, you consent to such publication by Herschel Supply Co. or its service providers and agents. Please refer to the Terms of Use for additional provisions relating to user submissions that may apply to you.

##### Use of Your Personal information

Upon Herschel Supply Co.’s collection of your personal information, Herschel Supply Co. may use such personal information internally, separately or in combination with pre-existing information, for the following purposes:

  * To develop, enhance, market, sell or otherwise provide information, products or services
  * To establish and conduct commercial relationships, including to process purchases or other transactions and to conduct or administer other transactions that you may engage in with Herschel Supply Coon or through the Sites
  * To conduct or administer contests, sweepstakes or other promotions in which you have participated;
  * To contact you and to respond to any communications that you may have had with us;
  * To troubleshoot problems with the Sites and Services;
  * To customize your experience or homepage on the Sites;
  * To develop and manage Herschel Supply Co.’s business and operations;
  * To enforce Herschel Supply Co.’s Terms of Use or comply with this Privacy Policy;
  * To detect and protect Herschel Supply Co. and other third parties against error, negligence, breach of contract, fraud, theft and other illegal activity, and to audit compliance with Herschel Supply Co.’s policies and contractual obligations;
  * To engage in business transactions, including the purchase, sale, lease, merger, amalgamation or any other type of acquisition, disposal, securitization or financing involving Herschel Supply Co.:As permitted by, and to comply with, any legal or regulatory requirements or provisions;
  * To access, preserve, disclose and use your personal information contained in your account, all Submissions (as defined in the Terms of Use), all communications to and from you, all information relating to your use of the Sites, if Herschel Supply Co. is required to do so by law or legal process or if Herschel Supply Co. determines, in its sole discretion, that such action is necessary to protect the rights of Herschel Supply Co., third parties, and other users of the Sites or for purposes of responding to your request for customer service; or
  * For any other purpose to which you consent.

Personal information collected by Herschel Supply Co. may be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States, Canada, Hong Kong or Australia. While in another jurisdiction for processing, the information may be accessed by the courts, law enforcement, and national security authorities of that jurisdiction.

##### Disclosure of Your Information

Herschel Supply Co. may disclose your personal information to its subsidiaries or affiliates and to third parties whom Herschel Supply Co. hires to provide services on Herschel Supply Co.’s behalf, including, but not limited to, support services, website services, delivering promotional materials, contests, sweepstakes and other promotions, and answering customer questions about Herschel Supply Co.’s products and services. These subsidiaries, affiliates and third parties may be located overseas. Herschel Supply Co. will only provide those third parties with the personal information that they need to deliver the services to Herschel Supply Co. and/or on Herschel Supply Co.’s behalf. Herschel Supply Co. will not disclose your personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes without obtaining prior affirmative consent. In the event that Herschel Supply Co. is involved in a business transaction, including the purchase, sale, lease, merger, amalgamation or any other type of acquisition, disposal, securitization or financing involving Herschel Supply Co., you consent to your personal information and any other information Herschel Supply Co. may have collected being transferred to another party in connection with such transaction. You also consent to Herschel Supply Co. disclosing your personal information to legal, financial, insurance, or other advisors in connection with such business transaction or management of all or part of Herschel Supply Co.’s business or operations; as consented to by you from time to time, including to fulfill any other purposes that are identified when the personal information is collected; or as otherwise permitted or required by law.

##### Retention of Your Personal information

The personal information that you provide will be retained by Herschel Supply Co. in accordance with applicable laws. However, Herschel Supply Co. will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information it holds if it is no longer needed for Herschel Supply Co. business purposes.

##### Children’s Privacy

Herschel Supply Co. recognizes the privacy interests of children and Herschel Supply Co. encourages parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. The Sites are not intended for children under the age of 18. Herschel Supply Co. does not target its services or the Sites to children under 18. Herschel Supply Co. does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18.

##### Choice and Opt-Out Preferences

Herschel Supply Co. does not collect your personal information unless you choose to provide it. If, at any time, you prefer not to receive further email communications from Herschel Supply Co. (except in connection with information, products or services that you specifically request), you will have the ability to unsubscribe from such communications by means of a link provided in every broadcast e-mail that is sent to you by Herschel Supply Co. If, at any time, you prefer not to receive any other form of communication from Herschel Supply Co., you will have the ability to unsubscribe from such communications by contacting: [email@herschelsupply.com](mailto:email@herschelsupply.com).

##### Access and Correction

Herschel Supply Co. will take reasonable steps to ensure the personal information it holds is accurate, complete and up to date. Upon your written request, subject to certain exceptions provided by law, Herschel Supply Co. will inform you of the existence, use and disclosure of your personal information and give you access to that information. Additionally, if you have any questions or enquiries relating to our privacy practices or procedures, or if you believe that the personal information that Herschel Supply Co. holds about you is not accurate, complete or up to date you may write to the Privacy Officer at the address provided below. If you are able to establish that the information is not accurate, complete or up to date, Herschel Supply Co. will take reasonable steps to correct the information so that it is accurate, complete and up to date.

##### Request for Access and Correction, Questions or Comments

Herschel Supply Co. welcomes questions and comments about this Privacy Policy. Requests for access and correction of your personal information, and questions or comments should be directed to the Herschel Supply Co. Privacy Officer at:

Herschel Supply Co.  
Attention: Privacy Officer  
327 – 611 Alexander St  
Vancouver, BC  
V6A 1E1  
Canada
